Take this!
Why?!
M-Miyo-chan!
You were wide open!
U-unbelievable...
To think that such a fun
night turned out like this...
(Woo-HOO!)
It's there? It's gone?!
(It's gone?!)
Absent? Present!
(Present!)
Affixed, Guess I'm fixed?
Huh? Which one is it?! Trance, trance, trance!
It's dair? It's nought!
(It's nought!)
ONIMAI: Onii-chan is Done For!
AbSENT? pRE:sent!
(pRE:sent!)
ONIMAI: Onii-chan is Done For!
The Why of [I], erodes!
Mahiro Oyama
Farewell to UV light, indoor guard at the ready!
Bye-bye, alright! Best to stay inside all day!
That will of mine's up and done willed itself away!
Mihari Oyama
Fight, flight, out like a light! Back to my home I go!
Aah, a world unknown,
it met with my gaze and flashed a smile
It pulls me in, this may just be worth my whiiile
Hey, check it out,
this water's as sweet as paradise!
Fashion, to make-up, hairstyles et al,
Within the garden of maidens, dancing takes bloom!
Wha, madame? Who's that? Guy's the I, no lie!
(Who!)
(Are!)
(It's me!)
I don't know what's happening, my fragile identity
Begins anew right now, a sense of wonder!
(Woo-HOO!)
At this rate, maybe my very psyche will fade and melt!
Now arise! Heed my call! Go forth, pillar of self!
(Hey!)
(Pillar of self!)
Let's edge our best, so we can see a happy end!
It's there? It's gone?!
(It's gone?!)
Absent? Present!
(Present!)
Affixed, guess I'm fixed?
Huh? Which one is it?! Trance, trance, trance!
ONIMAI: Onii-chan is Done For!
It's dair? It's nought!
(It's nought!)
AbSENT? pRE:sent!
(pRE:sent!)
The Why of [I]-dentity, will crumble forth!
Winter break is the best!
After many trials and tribulations,
through thick and thin,
#08  Mahiro's First Girls-only Sleepover
I've finally reached paradise...
Now I can slack off to my heart's content!
Long breaks really are
dangerous, aren't they...
At this rate, he'll wind up as a
failure of a person all over again...
That's it!
Contact List
Family
Friends
Non-School
Relatives
University
Research
Adjacent
Chitose Azuma
Kaede Hozuki
Tsubasa Inui
Arika Tachimi
Mai Katou
Kobayashi Nami
Aika Honma
Kaede
You're welcome.
Thank you so much!
Don't mention it.
Well, I'm gonna
head to bed now.
Good night!
Onii-chan | Now | Kaede | Sure
Can Momiji-chan
Can Momij
stay the
Now then...!
Can't just sit around while the clock ticks away
at such an important and limited time of leisure.
All right!
Let's graph out a schedule.
In the morning, let's sleep a whole bunch,
and at night, I really want to take it easy.
So with that in mind...
Anime
Sleep
Meal
Video
Games
Meal
Manga
I-It's perfect.
Well, without further ado!
Until dinner, the grand single-player
gaming rally is now on the menu!
After all that, didn't you just wind up
with the same plan as always?
Gaia herself has willed me
to slack off like this!
This is my Winter Vacation Style!
Honestly...
M-Mihari?
Wanna have a throwdown?
Not today.
Oh, they're here, they're here!
This development can't possibly be...
Sorry to intrude!
Yoo-hoo~!
Good day!
So many came...!
Y-you're gonna go and
drag me outside, aren't you!?
I'm not falling for that trick!
I heard we were having a fun
sleepover today, though....
Huh?
Mahiro-chan, didn't you invite us?
Sorry for intruding!
A s-sleepover?
What the heck are you all talkin—
I brought my pajamas and everything!
I brought mine too!
Me too, me too!
Oh?
Mahiro-chan, were you playing a game?
Oooh!
Mahiro, let us play, let us play!
Ooh, sure thing!
Ah, but this is only a two-player game...
Ta-da!
Therefore...
Family Go-Kart Racing
Onee-chan has a present for you!
Whoa!
Right on point!
Whoa, that was close!
All right, bombs away!
I can just dodge it, you know!
Dodge, you say...
Aaah! I'm gonna get hit!
Goooooo!
Dinner's ready!
Got it!
Onimai.
ONIMAI
Thanks for the meal!
As expected, the doctor's
cooking is so tasty, ain't it!
I told you, I'm not a doctor~!
All right, bring over your empty plates.
Well then, Mahiron.
It was a punishment game, after all.
You were the one talking such a big game.
My condolences.
Its not like that, I just let them win.
They're our guests, after all...!
If that's the case, don't you seem a bit too vexed?
After all, games are more fun to
play with others, aren't they?
Let's play that game again sometime.
Th-That... depends on the game.
Yeah!
It was fun, wasn't it?
I wanna play again.
Can't be honest with ourselves, can we?
What's the big idea...?
I'm done...
Nice work!
Good job!
Now then, shall we continue our gaming?
It's already late. We'd bother
the neighbors, wouldn't we?
Plus, I worked up a sweat, so
I wanna take a bath first.
Right?
Hmm...
Well then, I don't mind going
last, so let's take turns—
Let's split up into pairs!
If we go in one at a time, the water'll
eventually get cold, won't it?!
Th-That's a terrible idea!
Why's that?
I-It's just... Um...
All right, then! Mahiron!
I can wash your back...!
I-In that case, I can...
wash your hair too!
Um...
Er...
Now, now.
Settle down, you two.
Miyo-chan!
How about we go back to our roots and
give the [AsaMomi] pairing a consideration?
Asa?
Momi?
No good! She's downright degenerate!
Er, so you mean, Asahi
and I should compete over it?
Ooh! You wanna go~?
All right!
Rock-paper-scissors, then!
All right, Asahi's gonna throw rock!
Hold it, hold it!
I-I-I'll...
Uhyaaa—?!
Take responsibility.
We'll bathe together.
E-eeh?!
U-Um...
At this kind of distance, being
looked at is certainly a little...
You've gotten bigger, huh?
Wha?! That's sexual harassment!
That's not what I meant!
See, we used to bathe together
when we were little, didn't we?
I was just reminiscing.
And on your end, you've
gotten smaller, haven't you.
Just whose fault is that?!
The bath's freed up! Go ahead, you're next.
Ooooh!
You're so cute, Mahiro-chan!
Mahiron, you smell so gooood!
Eeeehhh?
It's the shampoo's scent, isn't it!?
Here! Let's get in that bath, Asahi!
Uwaraba!
Miyo-chan, you hurry up too!
B-But it'll be too cramped
with the three of us.
Now, now. Since we have the opportunity,
we might as well get in together!
You can wash up first, Miyo-chan.
Asahi will go ahead and
get in the tub with her.
G-got it...
Their gaze is stabbing into
my back like a bunch of thorns...!
Getting to see these two interact
up close is delectable, though.
Blub, blub, blub, blub.
It's been so long since Asahi
and I last bathed together, huh?
Do you remember?
Hm?
Back when we first became friends...
It's Asahi!
I'm Momiji. Nice to meet you!
It's a topknot! You're a samurai!
Nice to meet you, Momijiro!
Mo-mi-ji!
It's so neat! Topknots are so neat!
Maybe Asahi should tie her hair up too.
You're such an odd one, aren't you?
If you want to try it, then...
Look! It's cute!
Hup!
Take that!
Yay!
Wanna take a bath?
Sure!
It's fine if we go in together, right?
Oh! Did you not want to?
N-No, it doesn't bother me.
Asahi bathes with her
'nii-chan all the time, after all...
Does it grow in later?
What does?
I know it was when we were little,
but that was still pretty rude, y'know.
Araaaa...
We used to wash each other too, didn't we?
You simply must reenact it here and now!
All right, then, Miyochin...
Hueh?
I'll wash ya!
E-er, I didn't mean me...
Now, now! No need to be modest!
It actually feels kinda nice...
It's 'cause I used to wash my
'nii-chan's back all the time, y'know!
Okay! Raise your hands!
We're going for your underarms!
That was a bit of a shock.
ONIMAI
Onimai.
Mahiro
Is it really okay for us to
all be in the same room...?
Since it's a sleepover, wouldn't it be
weirder to sleep separately?
Or perhaps, would you rather spend the
night with your Onee-chan, I wonder?
I already apologized about
the whole bath thing!
Well, it'll be fine, won't it?
Onii-chan, you wouldn't hurt a fly, after all.
Good grief, what kind of
person do you think I am?
There's futons!
The excitement's rising, isn't it!
Asahi, you're in the way!
Was it cramped in the bath
with three people?
It wasn't a problem at all.
Th-Though we did have a bit of an incident...
Oooh!
You look so mature, Miyo-chan!
I'm just the type who merely watches, okay!?
Eh?
For now, let's just leave her to herself...
What on Earth happened in that bath...?
Well, you all can take it leisurely from here.
Don't stay up all night, okay?
Bye-bye, doctor!
Good night!
Okay, what now? What are we doing?!
Whoa, there!
For now, let's just decide on our futons.
I'll sleep here.
It's my own futon, after all.
The one next-door is mine!
No fair!
Let's rock-paper-scissors for it this time!
All right! I'm going with scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I was facing Asahi, of course
I read too much into it...
Victory goes to the honest!
Be careful, Mahiro-chan.
Asahi's terrible at sleeping soundly, after all.
Eh? Really? I don't
wanna deal with that...
It's fine, it's fine!
Take this!
You little...
You've done it now!
Whoops.
Hey...
This isn't a field trip, you know?
Yooooooou...!
We got her mad!
Sorry, Mahiro-chan!
Take this! Vanishing pillow!
Keep it down, will you?!
ONIMAI
Onimai.
Asahi, this is your fault, y'know?
Momiji was playing along too, though.
Well, let's just try to keep
it down from now on.
Then...
It's time to roll out the red carpet
for the long-awaited girls' talk!
Oh, Miyo-chan's back to life?
Chitchat is the real meat of a sleepover!
I see.
I'm a little hesitant, though.
Hey, hey! What should we talk about?
Love gossip, perhaps?
It's gotta be love gossip, right!
Well then, Asahi will take the lead.
Eh?!
It's a fearsome fable...
of the Pillow Flipper yokai!
This is Asahi's very own firsthand experience...
As Asahi slumbers away, night after night,
it appears before her pillowside...
Pillow, pillow, pillow...
It flips your pillow away from under your head,
and even moves your body around...!
Pil...
This is girls' talk...?
That's just a spooky campfire story...
Stupid Asahi!
Why'd you have to bring
up such a scary story?!
H-Hey now, weren't you listening?
That wasn't scary at all!
No, no! I can't hear you!
I didn't think she'd react this badly...
You knew she was bad with this stuff?
You're a bad girl, aren't you?
I'm going straight to sleep!
I'm sorry, okay...!
Eeeehh...! What about our love gossip...?
Momiji can be pretty cute
sometimes too, huh?
I'm turning off the light now!
Okay!
I really need to go to the bathroom...
Jeez, Asahi, you dummy...!
I'll just have to hold it in 'till morning...
So cold...
Where'd my comforter go?
She really can't sleep soundly, can she...
It's no use! She won't wake up at all!
I'm gonna catch a cold at this rate.
No other option...
Time for an emergency evacuation.
Momiji...
The Pillow Flipper
The Pillow Flipper?!
Eh?
I-I'm uh, sorry. Seriously.
D-don't worry too much about it!
It was my fault, anyway.
Just leave the rest to me.
Momiji, you can head on back and
use my futon instead, okay?
O-Okay...
Mahiro-chan, what will you do, then?
Hmm...
Oh!
Mihari
Eh?! What is it, what is it!?
Why are you here?
Don't ask for now, please.
Good night!
Ahh, this is so embarrassing!
I must have had too much
juice so late, you know?
So that's what happened...
Can't help that now.
You didn't have to take the
blame for me, you know?
It's fine, it's fine.
It'll be our little secret.
Y-You're sure?
Well, thank you.
It's totally fine.
I see, I see...
Huh...?
Where's Asahi-chan?
She's still sleeping upstairs.
Asahi's terrible at waking up too, y'know...?
It's the Pillow Flipper!
O-K, 1•2•3's our cue, hey~
Ehehe!
Come on! To the secret garden and away!
(Wooooo...!)
Onii—...Mahiro-chan, how about a maid outfit today?
No no, it's gotta be a bunnygirl suit, right?
Eh?
How about we try a pair of matching Hakamas!
E-err, um...!
Hey! Hold on!
Well either way, strip 'em off!
No, stooooooop!
Genius at the grind, subject has resigned
(From dusk to dawn~)
Drug status: It's a huge • suc • cess!
(Hold on, hold on!)
Cute gal acquired, now time to caress!
(Well now, go on~)
My pal's rewired, oh-ho yes!
(Snicker, snicker!)
Let's party woo-hoo, yay, yay, yay!
(Ain't that a black sheep within the girls' garden!?)
Adventure and yuri yuri bloomin' all night!
(Emotions all mixed up!)
O-K, 1•2•3's our cue, hey~
We've passed the ♂gender♀ borderline!
Ba-dump ba-dump, to the you
venturing to a new world:
Here we goooo!
(One!)
(Two!)
(Three!)
(Go Beyond World!)
(Woooo!)
W-w-w-well, whatever! That's just fine!
(W-woo!)
You win! I give up!
(Wooooo, yeah yeah!)
A girl's itty body holds oh so many
BIG ol' secrets yes indeed!
(Yeah! Yeah! Wooo!)
All one's might! Here's some fight!
(W-woo!)
Why, we may have quuuite the slight?
(Woooooo, yeah yeah!)
They say girl power, hey, is what makes the world go 'rooound!
(Yeah! Yeah! Yaaaaaay!)
(Nananana, nanana, nanana~)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
To my nigh Identity Cry-sis:
I'll see you again, some day!
Next Episode: Mahiro and the New Year's Holiday
Illustration:Toshiyuki Sato
See you next time!